I think technology is the future, but she has a many many problems because the students
are already exposed to this technology out of the school, so that's why I think we should
moderate that use and maybe we can put a
plage of of of hours still for example one hour for today and after we continue the
traditional way exercise like papers and books and I agree with you to
keep using books papers and traditional way of learning but in my opinion technology
provides extensive opportunities for students it's a way for them to develop new skills and their
creativity by using devices like tablets, computers etc and it's a new way of learning for them
it can develop their interest for what we we are studying and like you said they already use
electronic devices so developing learning by technology is really in our area and that's why I think
we should develop that point in the school yes but what do you think about the psychology of our
students if we expose too much our students to technology we know that it's a possibility for them
to develop anxiety and I think that can degrade their their relationships so I think we have
to take this in consideration and maybe don't put them really faster to the technology right now
yes I agree we should limit the use of technology in school like two hours per day maybe
that could be interesting to to experiment that way of learning what do you think about a class of
sensibilization we could make a place of sensibilization for parents and for students to show us
the danger of the technology and maybe debate of the benefits and yes I totally agree with you
I think it could be necessary to learn to parents and students the dangers of internet the
extreme use of electronic devices on health for example on the ice and concentration etc
and there is another thing we are not really agree for the technology using this school
I hope the technology will not
use for the homework because there is disparity social and I think that some students are not
the capacity or the materials way to have a computer that they're on or so I think it's important
to let the technology in into school yes or another solution is to ask parents if they have
electronic devices at home and for the students who don't have electronic devices to do homework
maybe school can provide us them a computer to to do their homeworks for example if they have to
do expose that could be a solution for them to to work at home with technology okay
time
what time do you think we should impose to use technology at school
you said two hours per day I am agree with that solution because I think two hours is not
too much one hour is is not enough okay but two hours you have the time to make many things
and I think it's enough okay and in what in what class do you think we should use it for
example plastic art mathematics English okay I think we can use for mathematics French
lesson just for grammar exercise one is about reduction I prefer paper of course but for just
simple exercise computer technology is great way and mathematics of course physical one is
possible SVT you can okay well you can use the technology for see video and it is more you know
attractive for students okay I agree I think we should put in place two hours per day for
these classes