You can do that number?
0.5
0.05
and I'm role A
and I'm a candidate 0.25
and I'm a role B
Okay, you can begin
So I personally think that new technologies
aren't any good in class
and it should be
something that is out of the school
and not in the school
Okay, I understand your point of view
but today the technology is quite important
because we need
computer to access to websites
or things like this
and teacher has
to show things to the class
or things like this
Yes, of course
I hear this
but I think that
there are some studies
that show that
there are two
kind of
of a situation
I think there is a
when there
are
everyday new technologies
and it can
represent a distraction
and of course
on the other side
there can be
once a week a class
with computers
to learn new technologies
to the
I agree
but I think that
the technologies
should be the
development of new
way with new technologies
to learn
and to teach
for the kids
it's a
better way to
learn because
they are more
happy to be there
they enjoy
the class
and teachers
it's
more simple
because
they can
use a lot of things
and diversify
the
how they work
Yes, but
we know
quite a time now
that the
device
is a great
huge
amount of time
like 6-8 hours
a day
so we do not need
to increase
this time
I agree with you
technology is
also
keyboard
or
the things
that can project an image
on the keyboard
and it's not just the computer
so if we invest
in the
research of new technology
we may
discover the new way
who
do not need to be on the
computer or
iPad or something like this
but who can
help the teacher
This is a good
point
if you want a new technology
in class this should be
with great equipment
not necessarily
a computer
but
there will be
some investment
that we need to do
and of course
there will be
an instruction of the teacher
because
not a teacher
knows how to use
keyboard or
computer
for their
course, for
mathematic, for example
there is
inequality between
school that has
the money for this
and school that
doesn't have. I know that and
the government
who has to help
this school
and this teacher
and also the parents
because maybe
the child is
in a
great school
but he may
have no money
but it's a government
who has to help
the school
offer them the
opportunity to
buy new stuff
I agree with you
so if the government
say that
you will invest in this
and of course
give money
to school that
doesn't have that much money
I can
eventually think
that some technology
has a certain level
with a
minimum amount of time
can be good
because
of course
this is not
all about
okay
but maybe we should
just talk about this
with the
governments
for communication
we try to
see what we can do
but I think that
even if we don't
know what the government
was going to say
we know that we have to
invest on your technology
because it's
too
important.
Yes, but
we have to invest
and to invest
in the future
that some people
like government
or
other kind of people
will help
and will do everything
they can
so there isn't any
inequality between
school and between students
because this is the future
sorry
this is the future
this was the
increase in equality
the government
will
choose to
invest.
it's an evidence
because there is too many
so many
how to say
that he
knows he has to do it
school need this for work, and work in a good way, because we saw that the child and the teacher are more
appears in the school when there is more technology.
Yes, of course, so maybe if this is on good regulation, technology can be slowly,
actually integrate in a classroom, but with regulation, not every day, like once a week, for example,
to start, or like one hour a day or something like this.
Yes, I agree with you, because we all know that the screen is bad for everyone, not just children.
And we, it's useful, but we have to regulate, as you say.
So the teacher do this part, they have to adapt with the things that we offer today.
And so we just had to agree with the fact that we invest, and that's it.
So I agree with you.
Okay.