036 Roll A
047 Roll B
Hello, colleague
Good morning
Ah, this is
We were asked to make suggestion to the supervisor
about the foundation prior it is
I'm actually really in favor to develop technologies
I'm not really
Well for me is like it's a tool
It's used in everyday life as a professional
or professionals use technologies every day
So we need to teach the students how to use it
in order for them to succeed in their professional life
Yeah, I agree with you but
You know some students are poor
Yeah
And some professionals are rich because they have a job
and they have a life, they have a family
And sometimes the students
even where they are immigrants
for example
they don't have any money to buy a computer
and it's difficult for those people to use computer at school
Yeah, I agree with you
That's why the school need to provide them
with computer and technology material
It's just school to provide them
such as the school provides books
For example
Yes, but books are less expensive than computers
School can't buy all computers for all students
Well, it is great because it's in investments
Like book needs to be changed every two or three years
and you have to buy like a way like a wide range of books
for every materials and for all the students
whereas when you have the computer
you only buy one computer and you have all the material on one computer
and it's used not for one student but for a lot of them
And if there is some degradation on the computer what you do
if some students break it or don't take care of a computer
what you do you change it and it's more expensive
that change your book
Well, it's more expensive but when students
degrades books they need to repay for it
so if they degrades the computer they will need to repay it
Yes, but repay a computer is too expensive for students
look at some manifestation in the streets
where students are poor
ask for money, ask for money for by food
for by an invitation and it's not possible for a student to buy a computer
as they want
Well, maybe if the computer says that school is safer for the material
like if they don't bring it at home
they only use it inside the school
maybe they are less risk to break it
So you want to make a mix like at school computer
and at home books
Yeah, so for me like using technology is really important
and to develop like creativity and safe learning
because it's more an intuitive way to learn
than just writing books and memorizing information
and so it's more like the learning to make projects to do research
and stuff like that so we give them more trust
and there are more ability for them to learn
Yes, but some studies show that we learn better with a book
while we're reading that while we're typing or we're searching on the internet
So it's more difficult for students to learn by a computer
than if they really read a book
I disagree with you about that
it might be true about writing
whereas typing on the computer
but actually when you search the information yourself
you'll like more interested in the task
so you will retain the information better
Yes, but you can also sell the information in the book
and you can write it by your hand
and it will be better for your memory
by my personal experience
I know that to learn something I had to read it, I had to learn it
and if I only type it on the computer I come to go to exam and succeed
Yeah, school is not only about learning information
in order to put it in the exam
it's also about learning how to search, how to make projects
how to create something and how to research the information
in order to learn more or to develop some competence
So for that I think the technology is the right tools and not books
I agree but look, for example, we are in Africa but in Africa
they can't have a book already
and if we want to reorganize the school system
that means that some people that can't buy a book
have to buy a computer, it's impossible
Yeah, of course we need to put finances into our budget
to finance all these projects
And you think...
And of course education comes first before technology
So in Africa, education even if it starts with book
and then can involve with technology is more important
but if we want them to really succeed
they need to learn how to use all the tools
they're going to use in their professional life
That's why for me we need to increase our technology teaching
but for that the teachers need to be formed as well
they cannot just put the child in front of the computer
and let them do their thing, they need to guide them
and that way we are not in the system where the teacher is on the shelf
and like the students are behind him
but it's more cooperative when the teacher only guides them
and the students are all safe learning or self-creating
Yes, but you have to buy computers
you have to teach how to use computers
you have to say at some teacher that are old
that are learning all of those teachers are not able to use computers
because they learn school with books
they are learning school with writing at the hand
so that's mean that we need to teach everything
and I think it's a little bit complicated in one second
so I argue with you with all what you said
but we have to make a transition
not to stop all of book and to pass all of computers
yeah, not what I said
actually we just need to increase the work in the teaching we do with technologies
and the age of the teacher doesn't matter
actually teachers need to be formed
because science is always evolving for example
we're not saying that the earth is flat nowadays
so teachers always have to learn in order to teach
and if the teachers learn about technology the age of the teacher really doesn't matter
so for me it's really important and education is always about teaching and learning
where has your students or a teacher
I agree with you so we can make some agreement
yeah maybe just increase like technology class
a little bit not too much
because it's dangerous for for economic of family
for economic of school it's a
it's an investment yes say the future it will go back
i agree with you it's more benefits
it's transition not too fast
okay we can go with the transition
okay perfect